<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Sushant Rajbanshi</title>
        <link>https://f0-x.github.io/</link>
        <description>Welcome to my Code Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0545</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://f0-x.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>ES6 Maps are underrated!</title>
    <link>https://f0-x.github.io/posts/js-map-vs-array/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0545</pubDate><guid>https://f0-x.github.io/posts/js-map-vs-array/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/maps-vs-array-feature-image.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Javascript Map is a rarely used data structure, hence it is not as widely understood as it would first appear, also is not as little as it first appears. We will start off with some fundamentals in this post and gradually head towards explaining the Map&rsquo;s function as well as certain situations in which it may be helpful.
The Big &#x2b55; Notation Understanding Big O Notation is crucial for analyzing the efficiency and scalability of algorithms and data structures.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Intuji UI Components ♾️</title>
    <link>https://f0-x.github.io/posts/ui-components/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 &#43;0545</pubDate><guid>https://f0-x.github.io/posts/ui-components/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/cover-image.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The Need for a Robust UI Component Library As our web application grew in complexity, we found ourselves constantly reinventing the wheel when it came to building user interfaces. Our development team was spending too much time creating and maintaining custom UI components, leading to inconsistent styles, duplicated code, and a suboptimal developer experience.
To address these challenges, we decided to invest in building a comprehensive UI component library that would serve as the foundation for our application&rsquo;s user interface.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>✨Shiny Skeleton Animation using TailwindCSS💨</title>
    <link>https://f0-x.github.io/posts/tailwind-skeleton/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0545</pubDate><guid>https://f0-x.github.io/posts/tailwind-skeleton/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/featured-image.gif" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Content loaders, skeleton screens, ghost elements, and content placeholders. These are the names given to the effect we&rsquo;ll be exploring today. Many companies, such as LinkedIn, Facebook, YouTube and Slack, use this effect in their apps and websites, as you may have noticed. As much as we developers want our websites to load as quickly as possible, there are times when a lot of data needs to be rendered on the page, so Skeleton screens are a great option.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
